risk facing criminal and civil liabilities for aiding and abetting genocide war crimes and
crimes against humanity under an international law and may face investigation and prosecution
the members of the state department face similar possibility again uh craig mokhyber who just
resigned as director of the new york office of the un high commissioner for human rights noted
that intent usually the hardest part of genocide to prove isn't in this case he wrote in his
resignation letter quote explicit statements of intent by leaders in the israeli government and
military leave no room for doubt or debate you claim that you want israel to make the distinction
but you don't seem to be decking just making the we absolutely if i might i didn't interrupt you
i didn't interrupt you the center for constitutional rights just put out a statement legal organizations
put members of congress on notice for complicity on genocide quote please take note this is a letter
that they sent to members of congress center for constitutional rights please take notice that
should you vote in favor of that package the biden package for israel you risk facing criminal and
civil liabilities for aiding and abetting genocide war crimes and crimes against humanity under an
international law and may face investigation and prosecution do members of the state department
face similar possibility again uh sam as i said we have uh the u.s government has a a rigorous process
in place for evaluating whether something constitutes uh genocide and we have not made that assessment
but you continue